<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Smart Living</string>
    <string name="create_an_account">Create an Account</string>
    <string name="first_name">First Name</string>
    <string name="first_name_hint">Enter your first name</string>
    <string name="last_name">Last Name</string>
    <string name="last_name_hint">Enter your last name</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="email_hint">Enter your email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="password_hint">Enter your password</string>
    <string name="hide_password">Hide password</string>
    <string name="show_password">Show password</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions">By continuing you accept our\u00A0</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="and">\u00A0and\u00A0</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use">Terms of Use.</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="or">or</string>
    <string name="already_have_an_account">Already have an account?\u00A0</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="welcome_to_smart_living_app">Welcome to \nSmart Living!</string>
    <string name="welcome_text">Welcome to Smart Living – Your ultimate smart home companion! Seamlessly control your connected devices, create personalized routines, and receive smart suggestions for energy-saving practices. Whether you\'re optimizing your lighting, adjusting your devices, or your thermostat, Smart Living empowers you to manage your home effortlessly while reducing energy consumption. Experience the future of home automation today!</string>
    <string name="creator">Created by @ApostolisSiampanis</string>
    <string name="smart_living_logo">Smart Living Logo</string>
    <string name="dont_have_an_account_yet">Don’t have an account yet?\u00A0</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_header">Terms of Use</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_intro">These Terms and Conditions govern your use of the Smart Living mobile application provided by APOSIAMP ("we," "us," or "our"). By downloading, installing, or using the App, you agree to comply with and be bound by these Terms and Conditions.</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_license">\n1. License:</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_license_text">We grant you a limited, non-exclusive, non-transferable, revocable license to use the App for your personal, non-commercial purposes. You may not sublicense, sell, or distribute the App.</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_conduct">\n2. User Conduct:</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_conduct_text">You agree to use the App in compliance with all applicable laws and regulations. You further agree not to:\n• Use the App for any unlawful purpose.\n• Interfere with or disrupt the operation of the App.\n• Attempt to gain unauthorized access to any part of the App.\n• Transmit any viruses, worms, or other harmful code through the App.\n• Use the App to infringe upon the rights of others.</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_ip">\n3. Intellectual Property:</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_ip_text">All intellectual property rights in the App, including but not limited to copyrights, trademarks, and trade secrets, belong to us or our licensors. You may not copy, modify, or distribute any part of the App without our prior written consent.</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_liability">\n4. Limitation of Liability:</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_liability_text">To the fullest extent permitted by law, we shall not be liable for any indirect, incidental, special, consequential, or punitive damages arising out of or relating to your use of the App.</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_modifications">\n5. Modifications:</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_modifications_text">We reserve the right to modify or discontinue the App at any time without prior notice. We may also update these Terms and Conditions from time to time. Your continued use of the App after any such changes constitutes acceptance of the updated Terms and Conditions.</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_governing_law">\n6. Governing Law:</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_governing_law_text">These Terms and Conditions shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of Greece, without regard to its conflict of law principles.</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_contact_us">\n7. Contact Us:</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_contact_us_text">If you have any questions or concerns about these Terms and Conditions, please contact us at info@smartliving.gr.</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_acknowledgement">\nBy using the App, you acknowledge that you have read, understood and agree to be bound by these Terms and Conditions.</string>    <string name="privacy_policy_header">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_intro">APOSIAMP ("we," "us," or "our") operates the Smart Living mobile application. This Privacy Policy outlines how we collect, use, and disclose information obtained from users of the App.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_info_collect">\n1. Information We Collect:</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_info_collect_text">• Personal Information: We may collect personal information that you voluntarily provide to us, such as your name and email address.\n• Device Information: We may collect information about your device, including device type, operating system, unique device identifiers, and mobile network information.\n• Sensor Data: We may collect metrics from your device\'s sensors, such as humidity, temperature, and other environmental data.\n• Usage Information: We may collect information about how you use the App, including the pages you visit, the features you use, and your interactions with the App.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_use_info">\n2. How We Use Your Information:</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_use_info_text">We may use the information we collect for the following purposes:\n• To provide and improve the App and our services.\n• To monitor and analyze sensor data to enhance the smart home experience.\n• To communicate with you, respond to your inquiries, and provide customer support.\n• To personalize your experience and tailor content and advertisements to your interests.\n• To analyze trends and usage patterns and optimize the performance of the App.\n• To comply with legal and regulatory requirements.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_share_info">\n3. How We Share Your Information:</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_share_info_text">We may share your information with third parties for the following purposes:\n• With service providers who assist us in operating the App and providing our services.\n• With our affiliates, partners, and other trusted third parties for marketing and promotional purposes.\n• With law enforcement agencies, government authorities, or other third parties when required by law or to protect our rights, property, or safety.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_data_security">\n4. Data Security:</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_data_security_text">We take reasonable measures to protect the security of your information and prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, or use. However, no method of transmission over the internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, and we cannot guarantee the absolute security of your information.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_children">\n5. Children\'s Privacy:</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_children_text">The App is not intended for children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If you believe that we have inadvertently collected information from a child under 13, please contact us immediately.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_changes">\n6. Changes to this Privacy Policy:</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_changes_text">We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect changes in our practices or legal requirements. We will notify you of any material changes by posting the updated Privacy Policy on the App or through other means.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_contact_us">\n7. Contact Us:</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_contact_us_text">If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, please contact us at info@smartliving.gr.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_acknowledgement">\nBy using the App, you consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="go_back">Go back</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="devices">Devices</string>
    <string name="routines">Routines</string>
    <string name="energy">Energy</string>
    <string name="indoor_temperature">Indoor Temperature</string>
    <string name="indoor_humidity">Indoor Humidity</string>
    <string name="heat_set_to">Heat set to</string>
    <string name="cool_set_to">Cool set to</string>
    <string name="auto_set_to">Auto set to</string>
    <string name="dry_set_to">Dry set to</string>
    <string name="degree_celcius">°C</string>
    <string name="percentage">%</string>
    <string name="turn_on">Turn On</string>
    <string name="turn_off">Turn Off</string>
    <string name="off">OFF</string>
    <string name="auto">Auto</string>
    <string name="cool">Cool</string>
    <string name="heat">Heat</string>
    <string name="dry">Dry</string>
    <string name="plus">+</string>
    <string name="minus">-</string>
    <string name="swing">Swing</string>
    <string name="change_direction">Change Direction</string>
    <string name="humidity">Humidity</string>
    <string name="silent">Silent</string>
    <string name="continuous">Continuous</string>
    <string name="set_to">Set to</string>
    <string name="max">Max</string>
    <string name="open_menu">Open Menu</string>
    <string name="close_menu">Close Menu</string>
    <string name="add">Add</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="about_intro">At Smart Living, our goal is to empower you to create a more efficient, comfortable, and sustainable home. Our app offers a seamless way to manage your smart home devices while providing valuable insights into your energy consumption.</string>
    <string name="about_our_features">\nOur Features:</string>
    <string name="about_unified_control">\n• Unified Control:</string>
    <string name="about_unified_control_text">Easily control and monitor all your smart home devices from a single, intuitive interface.</string>
    <string name="about_energy_monitoring">\n• Energy Monitoring:</string>
    <string name="about_energy_monitoring_text">Stay informed about your energy usage with real-time data on the power consumption of your devices.</string>
    <string name="about_user_friendly">\n• User-Friendly Design:</string>
    <string name="about_user_friendly_text">Navigate your smart home effortlessly with a clean, user-focused design that makes managing your devices a breeze.</string>
    <string name="about_our_vision">\nOur Vision:</string>
    <string name="about_our_vision_text">We envision a future where technology enhances your everyday life by making your home smarter, more connected, and energy-efficient. Our dedicated team is committed to providing you with innovative tools and insights that help you take control of your smart home and make informed decisions to reduce energy consumption and live more sustainably.</string>
    <string name="apostolis_siampanis">ApostolisSiampanis</string>
    <string name="github_profile">GitHub Profile</string>
    <string name="add_a_new_room">Add a New Room</string>
    <string name="add_a_new_device">Add a New Device</string>
    <string name="drawer_image">Drawer Image</string>
</resources>